Yo, the veil is thin the mic is hot welcome to the show where the truth gets caught
Drama meets destiny cats on patrol tarot cards flip while we bear the soul spawns a steps up pays 10 opens the door
Then the panel pops off like never before from trolls to truth. There's witches and kings
Everybody's welcome. Just mine. What you bring?
And tea that's divine pull up you see you're right on time
You're right on time
From shadow work Saturdays to soul truth Sundays panel so packed they're spilling out runways
Lenors on your shoulder tricks got the vibe low the Rudy marbles. It's a feline tribe got beta page Christine in the mid
universe family messy and slick we go deep we go real we cast and reveal if the
cards don't scare you the trolls sure will
oh my god that was good though okay that's that was i have the uh that last episode
up until the porn bomb i haven't saved on on stream yard so maybe i can
page actually come hi guys oh i can't believe that that sucked like it was such a good interview
and so much fun and like so cool and then like someone porn bombed under trevor's name
I know there was a trouble.
That was terrible.
Thank you, Andrew, for coming on the show.
Thank you.
I wrote him on Snapchat.
He said he would come back anytime.
Let's have him on again soon.
I'll see if he gets some people in his chat.
If he can post his channel again, I will.
Yeah, but go say hi to him and watch him.
He seems like a really nice guy too, a really nice guy.
So thank you so much for being on the show
and I'm sorry for the foreign bomb.
That was unfortunate.
Oh, thank you Electra too.
DJ Electra became a member again.
Thank you so much.
That's awesome.
Thank you guys.
Things are going well.
I got these new cards.
This is called the believe in your own magic oracle deck. It looks really cool
So I'll do like a little three cards for the chat with these
This is a brand new deck. I just got this today. It looks really nice. It has a nice
You know, they're a little bit thin just a little bit thin
But let's put these cards are actually nice and easy to shuffle. I really like to shuffle these cards
They're like it's just easy to maneuver my hands they're
Like some expensive decks are like the hardest shuffle and like some like inexpensive decks are easy. So I'm just gonna do a nice shuffle
get these all
Wind up I'm actually okay at shuffling and some people say oh you can't shuffle. I'm pretty good. I'm like not bad
It's like those picking like you're pretty fast. Sometimes they flip over
So, but these are actually, yeah, these are actually
Shuffling pretty well
Like
It's so funny people would say oh these are sometimes it's more less expensive things are better sometimes
It'll be nourished sometimes
You go ahead expensive condiment was disgusting and then like you just get some dollar 99 a1 sauce. It's like good on everything
Okay, what do we got?
Ooh, this says sun.
Paint the sun back into your sky.
That's a beautiful card.
So she's a painter painting the sun back into the sky.
Number 11.
Paint the sun back into your sky.
Hey, Summer, we're just checking out these new cars.
Summer, you missed the bodybuilder.
I had a bodybuilder in the chat.
But I had to delete it because it's a porn bomb got a porn bomb
Next we got thrown it says your potential is endless and it's got like a mermaid pretty cool
The throne your potential is endless there. They aren't the throne
I've got like a witch and mermaid and a princess
Maybe those are like
Three aspects of the same person
Archetypes the throne
Uh-oh, hold on one second is my
Hello, hold on
Have you been hearing me?
Hawaii's gonna get see I mean I haven't gotten any tsunami warnings on my phone
I would think I'd get a message on my phone that would save
Warning, so I think I'm okay. The beach seems calm
Hi everybody
Yeah
Yeah, Nancy I have it saved on on stream yard. I just uh, I'm just afraid of having it saved on YouTube, right?
But this one says evil queen you deserve sugar not salt says evil queen
Look at the nails
Interesting you deserve sugar not salt
Okay, hopefully those messages were interesting that
Pretty cool deck. I liked it
Let's see, I can't put people in jail for trolling. Well, did I say that I?
Say that I was gonna do that put people in jail. I
Mean some people can't what I say about trolling I like put people in jail. What do you mean? I
Deal with it. I deal with it every day. What are you talking about?
There's my link. Let's do open panel tonight. What the heck?
Feel like I should give back to the
Back to the chat because there's a lot of generosity been thrown at me and I wouldn't really want to say thank you to your guys
And I don't want you guys to think I'm all about
You have auto on stage hold on
No, uh, uh, it was gonna be a porn bomb
Wow guys, wow this Wow
Hey Garrett, hey, Jamie's Cowboys. Hey everybody. Yeah, so
I finished those coffees pretty quick. I inhaled those coffees, you know, I held two coffees like nothing
In little and smoking is this vape is weed vaping it gets me kind of tired
But hopefully somebody will come up it's not a porn bomber everyone's welcome up right now come on up
Hopefully daddy think this will come back to chat you guys like that. I saw him today. I was like, hey come come by my chat and say hi
We'll hopefully I'll
Get you some subscribers and
new friends
Because he's a nice guy. I see I see good people and I want to help them so
Can I say one thing psyche? I didn't mean to say this the Orioles have well one run lead
But the Blue Jays have second and third with two outs in the bottom of the night
So we got to get one more out will win you look at them good tonight's psyche if I may say so myself
You're looking a little pink. Thank you. Oh red
I'm good. How are you? I'm good to see you
But it's boba shit. I'm not gonna show my TV, but I'm watching the game. Let me not talk about baseball. I thought oh
You're looking like a little like a frog almost
Don't say it
Strike two we got one one ball one strike psyche. I'm sorry. Why would you say it again?
Are you keep saying I said the D word dumbass? No, I
That's what doesn't God he said, but I don't know
Here's how you doing man fine. How are you?
Same old another day in paradise psyche. I know it's so quick, Goddy
I'm not really
Let's play this is a fucking art
Yeah
Like it like took away of my like desire to talk to him like a hundred percent
And just like oh, I
Don't know we don't need to insert replay. Oh
Hey, the one person that comes up he has to do it like
It should be okay
Anyway, I got me all just drain me
I don't know, and I feel like sleeping can thank Joe for that.
God
It's like a psychic vampires
Okay
Yeah, I slept most of the day
You know, I just had two coffees so I shouldn't be tired
Me some tobacco my ball, I don't know
I suddenly feel so drained
25 people in the room shit
Seriously that got me like cross-eyed. Oh my god
Hello, dude, what's going on?
I don't know why you let these words have power over you like this. It's first of all, I understand your concern
Second of all, don't like don't act like it's the end of the world. I know but it's like he just keeps doing it
I keep telling like
For no reason it's like it's kind of like it feels like an attack after a while if like you can't like respect the one rule
I'm giving you know basically, but it's it's not just him if people see that it bothers you gonna keep doing it to you
That's why you got to get rid of that power. It has over you. Yeah. Well, it's just like it's just against the TOS is the only thing
So it's like the I don't think it's actually a TOS thing. Everybody says it everywhere apparently
Well, not like it's hard. Yeah, he was saying it all day
Yeah, but he's not monetized. Is he monetized? I don't know if he's monetized like if you're not monetized
I didn't check you might be yeah, because I'm monetized and so it makes it's kind of a bigger deal like these TOS things
Which is why I have you know
People that are not monetized can get away with that or you know, even if they are it's like it's just a way it's said it
But it's like it's the hard ER
It's like and then people are like they bomb with the bomb porn bomb with it. They
And it's just like, it just feels like an ugly word.
I just don't like the word at all.
I agree, I agree.
I don't use the word personally, but I agree with you.
Yeah.
But you can't let it have so much power over you
that it ruins your whole night.
Look at you, you're all happy and now you're like,
devastated.
Uh, you know, well, it's like, it's just like, uh, like on last night, the, the beat is like trying to like troll me with the word biscuit.
And it's like, it's like, I really don't care.
It was like one of those things where it's like, it's just being used to troll me.
It doesn't mean anything or whatever.
It's just like, it's the only reason you would use it.
It's just to troll me to like this.
It's like, that's all it means.
It's just like a troll of me.
And so.
But then now she's like making a bigger deal and like playing making music videos about it and it's like I don't care
But it's like the thing is it's like
I'd rather have like do something that was meaningless be a troll than like it's like some kind of meaningful troll
And so it's like it's almost like I redirected it towards that but on purpose, but it's fine
Like I don't know so everyone's gonna say biscuit like it's like it means something to me, but it doesn't it's just a troll
I don't know people you're getting sensitive. You're getting too sensitive. I'm not being critical. You're just getting too sensitive
Yeah, I know okay
It's okay. I know I'm like a little bit sensitive today
It depends on the day I guess and what's going on. Yeah, I don't know.
Kind of feel low energy today. I'm kind of like just like
I was gonna come up. I was gonna come up and say the end word, but I'm not gonna pile on. Oh, thank you. Appreciate that. No problem pal
I love you any time any time. I'm having a good day. Hopefully you're having a good day
Yeah, it's a pretty good day
I had to bust my ass for about three hours, but otherwise it's been alright. How'd you like the guests?
I was a special guest. I invited from his show to my show
He was alright. I didn't know he was legit once he turned his camera on. I'm like, whoa, whoa, whoa
That's that's a weightlifter. No, then I realized he's a powerlifter
Yeah, that's what he said. He was yeah power lifter. Yes. All right. Once he said once I realized he's a power lifter that it made sense
Yeah, he had these huge breasts basically, but that all that upper body mass
He's gonna help him lift whatever he's lifted. He said it's 650 deadlift
Yeah, whoa. Yeah, he does what he does one he does one rep at a time like he's like a lift at once and make
His backward fucking snap. Yeah
I mean the most I could deadlift was maybe 354 at my at my best
Are you a bodybuilder?
I would just wait lifting weights at the time. Mm-hmm
Wow, please I'm pretty strong. I know I'm like 100 hundred and forty hundred two pounds six foot three
I'm like a twig at this point. Did you're 103?
No, no hundred and hundred and thirty five hundred and forty pounds is six foot three. Oh, that's only because you're tall
Yeah, we're tall you'd be under a hundred. Yeah, that would be under a hundred. Oh my god eat more man
You're not eating enough. It's all my skill. It's all my extra skeleton
Yeah, well, I have like I have like a lot of food to eat from like last night
I got a big got a big dinner delivered and so I have a lot of that left to eat tonight
So it goes backstage. You want to apologize? He said, oh
Here's a beat it to beat it to beat us backstage. Yeah, hold on
She brought the biscuit and he brought the don't say that don't don't say biscuit. He's gonna sue us
I didn't say biscuit. I would never hurt you sound like yeah, I apologize
What are you talking about psyche?
You said I'm trolling you because I like the song Taste the Biscuit.
What's why the Joe or his t-shirt?
You think everything is about you?
Like, that's a joke.
Like, we love that song.
God, he loves that song.
Everybody likes to taste the biscuit.
I know, but it's all about me.
I'm getting tags.
Sweet Pea tags me in the videos.
And like, you all, like, say that it's like, it's like a...
It's not a corn bomb.
Like, it's called Taste the Biscuit.
It's a song.
It's not making fun of you.
They're making fun with you, bro.
Oh, yeah.
Sure, they are.
Sure, whatever.
I listened to it last night with my friend like I was over at her place and I was like,
hey, can we listen to this? And she never heard it and she liked it. She didn't think I was trolling
her. It's so corny. Did you make out? It's great. Fine, I'll pick another song that you might like better.
just sing it to us beat-up you don't want to play it just sing it to us please
He will start crying he'll get mad at me
I think he's good. I can just see him like having a nightmare like all these biscuits are chasing him down
Don't think of that don't scare the guy don't scare what a great group of friends you got second
there's biscuits ready for like I didn't say take taste the coach it's a biscuit
Look at his sweet little cat and still on camera his cat's still on panel. That's a cat right there boy
He's thinking what I do deserve you people. I
Mean he acts like I like did something horrible
I just like the song and then we wanted you to play it and then the more you didn't want to play it the more
We wanted to listen to it, you know
Like well that is kind of this respectful beta. He's good. He's good. He's over it. I don't know how it's I don't know why I can't figure it out
Can anyone tell me why I taste the biscuit?
They have you ever tasted the biscuit? Yes. Yeah, I'm KFC with the butter top and the honey sauce
Oh, that's a good one.
Honey sauce.
It's good when it's sweet.
I don't like the sour one.
Don't talk about it anymore.
I had a sour one once.
It wasn't good.
I'm just really confused because people say the worst things and they porn mom you and they say the n-word and all this stuff and then you think I'm trolling you with a song called taste a biscuit
The other
That came out 12 years ago and has like 3.5 million viewers
Body said a joke that Joe only said the word diggers
But when I came on slice panel and the girls like I only said the d-word like I didn't mean to say it
I don't should even say anything that ends with the R. That's what anybody
Even if you say happier if happy or ends in ER don't say it. Oh
We live in that this ain't a joke
Shut up psyche. Should I leave? Am I gonna annoy you?
Please don't leave me though. He's taking a nap. Our psyche. Yeah, psyche
Well, he's under a cookie
Can you at least come over here and talk to us because the host of the channel your dad is sleeping
I love that fucking cat that's a good cat. He's protecting his dad right there. That's a cat that protects his his owner
I don't know how to talk to them
I think I came up to like just joke with psyche, but it just gets worse and worse. I don't know. He just I don't know
Take that take it take the butt plug out of your butt. It's been up there too long
Once he eats something he'll be fine, okay, okay
Send him a biscuit
Oh, that's a good idea
You're awful
So I keep you like KFC oh
Jesus is the joke coming. No, he doesn't beat a lot as a good one
I don't know. I mean, I think it's not that great, but at least the biscuits are good. You know, it's the only thing that's good
He just likes this. He got hungry. I saw that Joe. You just got hungry when I said
Yeah, I hear biscuits like KFC like god
They're fat. I don't really go to KFC anymore. No offense. I'm not going to say why because it'll be racist
There's a point I'm trying to give you like it takes so long to wait for your food like oh just pull over in the parking lot
We'll bring your food out to you. I thought it was a drive-thru. I don't want to sit your parking lot
You go to the wrong place. Yeah, I had KFC today. It took two minutes. It was good. I
Love you guys. I'm only fucking buzzing because it's football season coming up. I'm so excited. It's football season at the start
Sorry, sorry
I'm a real man. I like sports
What is this a sleep stream?
Yeah
Are you awake? Who died? Oh
Michael Lake was umo
You used to be up here on your panel all the time. Did you do like a remembrance for the guy?
Yeah, I um, I made a title called why spend mine when I can spend yours
It wasn't spend your money were you laughing at that's your money you talking about and you're laughing
He would want everybody to joke on and laugh on
that's so messed up
this ain't a fucking joke, this is serious business
I don't think I would have
maybe left Tracy money in his will
oh, now that's, you know what, I'm calling him
I'm psyching
you're going to jail
get it from Merna
Hey, don't learn it's available Frank cold-fiking be like, hey is your refrigerator running?
He'll be like yeah, but get off your fucking couch and go catch it you piece of shit. Sorry. It's like yeah, I love
God
Psyche you thought don't tell me to come up here, and I'm gonna sleep
Beat a joint and then I come up there, and you make a fool out of me, right because you just want to go to sleep
Oh my god, Joe just run into the devil
I'm with God God and the devil
Now I'm saying beat is the actual devil
We got a devil. We've got a witch and we got God. Oh, which really well
I don't know if somebody left me a message that are you practicing witchery?
I went up on I saw your panel you've got casting these spells with these little tea leaves or some shit
You were doing remember that so what you're doing spells with these tea leaves you were putting curses on people
I don't know how to do anything. I just play around.
We don't remember when you hurt people.
It worked apparently.
Oh, so it was proof then.
Oh, Michael, like with you.
I just don't get it. My cats, they make biscuits all day long with their paws.
They do the biscuit pausing. How can a person with like cats not like biscuits?
Like cats do biscuits or, you know, he gets so mad at me.
Your cats make you know, you know, he loves you, right? No, he doesn't
He's a fucking like man child who's always like cranked victim
Oh, no, this happened and I had a bad day because someone said the biscuit again like
He lets it go the next day
You guys are all buddy, buddy again. I'm trying to just like
You know
That's it. I tried my
But that's the way you two works God, I mean you should know because you're God
But that's the way you two works you drink and then the next day you just like hey nice to see you again
I don't have to drink because I do the same thing.
Oh, I do have to drink.
Yeah, Joe, good time to do that all day.
Just let it go.
You're just going to let it go, Joe.
That's it.
All right, I'll let it go.
I apologize.
How many times have you traumatized you, Joe?
And you just go back?
You have to apologize, Joe.
You understand.
I can't imagine how traumatized they are.
My eyes are going to crawl some so traumatized.
I don't even know if I'm right there.
Did you give Kim our $20 back?
Did you give her the $20 back?
Oh, I gave her 20 inches. What the hell? What does that supposed to mean?
Sorry about that. What was your question?
20 inches, like Jesus Christ. Have we got a wiffle ball pad in your pants?
No, she's not alive anymore.
She's not alive over here anymore.
She's not allowed over here anymore. This is personal.
She attacked me personally, and I don't think we'll be seeing Kim for help.
It was her birthday. It was her birthday a couple days ago.
Oh, you know what?
I wish she was never warned.
No, I'm sorry, no, I never said that, I was just kidding.
Here's the best stuff, I'm gonna tell her when you see me.
She's not allowed over, she didn't suspect me
so bad the other day, no vice business,
but let it be known from this day on, mark your words,
but she's packing my house,
because it ain't never gonna happen.
You don't disrespect your boy,
you don't disrespect your friend.
Canada Drive panel starting soon, really?
Yeah, okay. Where is he? I'm gonna go jump on there. He'll at least you'll engage in a conversation unlike psyche awakened terror and cats
But you're not gonna do that be though
You're gonna lay on your ground and talk to your cats and aggravate your cats like oh come
Yeah, me pet you and your cats are by like get
You're gonna tell us the rules before we even go there though. We can't just get there. What's the rule?
Yeah, make up the rules now. Yeah, make up a fucking rule. I got one you need one. I'll make up one
All right, I'm gonna go tear up buttercup tear up cutie for Judy tear up pumpkin. Cheer up biscuit
I'll see you soon. Bye. Get lost. I'll tell the Goddy. I'll drink my beer with you. God. He's right
She's such a fake motherfucker. Oh, so cheer up. I love you. I love you
You'll be calling a fucking horse tomorrow. You know when you're drunk
They don't come sweeter than beta
I love when beat is like I love you at the memory. She loved Janet. Well, she was a whore next week
Member competed loved another person. I don't give a I don't give a shit
I love to be to drink like I do because I hate all you motherfuckers
You got a drink. It's the only way to forget the next day you forget everything you can start fresh
That's the point of YouTube. That's the point of this community
The next day you have fun again, that's it man, you can't hold on to grudges
I tell this thing if you're exactly well said God, I'm not going to call you God. Your name's got me
Joe listen, I'm not gonna hold it against you. Just whatever you want to say
The point I'm trying to make is you're right if people that are so gay. Well, maybe I'm not saying gay
But like if people don't have their life
I've been coming on YouTube so much and I got aggravated over people on YouTube and I'm like I need a break
I can't if I'm gonna sit here and get aggravated over gay people. I need a fucking we grew up pre
2000 where being gay was mostly. Oh, you're being so fucking gay right now. Shut the fuck up
I mean stupid ass or like being a shithead. This is why we use the term gay
you know but today you just call me you fucking faggot you just call me that
fucking example oh it's an example i apologize i apologize
you're being so fucking gay right now just shut the fuck up we're like oh
you're being retarded you're acting retarded but now we can't say that we
can't say that anymore you don't call retar retarded you
call your friends retarded when they're acting
Retarded that's the way it's supposed to be like you like if you see a retarded guy acting retarded
You're not gonna say shut the fuck up. You're stupid retarded, you know
Like when I see beat on panel, did you hear me call be to retarded? She is but then I call it
No, I'm a gentleman. Thank you. I'm a gentleman. I'm a gentleman very kind
See we
Psychies in alcohol like psyche. We know what we're doing. You know, we have a
Man, we know you're listening psyche wake up. We know you can hear your little cocoon
Overdo it, you know, my god. I mean sometimes an accident slips though. Sometimes, you know, we make a mistake
We apologize
One time a Goddy. I was so drunk on panel most of the times I'm so drunk on panel like I see one time
Tripkit clicked me and I had to watch the clip and I didn't remember none of it
I had to watch myself not even remembering what I did. I was like, please be good, Joe
Don't even say the ad word now. That was a good man. Thank you
So what did you think? You're like, oh shit, you were embarrassed or you didn't give a fuck?
It's just embarrassing knowing you get so drunk and then you have to watch yourself clipped and you don't even remember
Like even saying any of the words on the clip like Jesus christ am I that blackout drunk?
I don't even remember getting clipped like that's that's kind of over the top. That's a little over the top
I say a lot of dumb shit every day. I forget it the next day 100 and I don't even drink
But when I hear it back, I'm like, yeah, that's something I would say
You know, and I'm like, you know, I'm not surprised by it.
There's times I see myself one-pound and I'm like,
well, I ever shut the fuck up, like, so I can hear myself think.
I'm like, oh, shit, that's me.
That's actually me talking so much.
And I'm like, I wish that gay guy Goddy would join,
like with his red little monkey eyes.
You remember when Sebastian was up on, uh,
Yeah, I remember that
Now I remember that he's fine
I like so I guess he has good guess myself not included but he does get good like good panels going I like to watch I
Can't hold the panel by myself. I'd need somebody to riff off of
it's not like one time and it was so much effort is just too much effort to go live I didn't mean to cut you all
big though, but I won't lie one time. It's just too much. It's too much. It's hard man.
You can't I could probably go like a half an hour not stop talking but after that it's like
I'm just not one of those people. I would just play five intros like Sandman and then five outros and not even say
work just ten songs and then try to try to collect like 50 bucks
Exactly. I might donate. I'm poor. You didn't donate to him, did you?
I'm 41 years old. I work every day of my life. I got to wake up tomorrow at 6 in the morning to go to work
I just I'm not saying I don't respect people to don't work
But I I'm so tired of like waking up in the morning and seeing these motherfuckers drunk from the next night
Like oh we're having so much fun. Of course you're having fun. You don't have nothing to do all day. Of course you're having fun
You're a fucking loser
Sorry, that was too far actually
No, I'm talking way too much
Is he gonna cut this off?
I think I think it's about to click it. I think I think Joe said more than I did. Oh
No, it's just it's just a shadow. It's the light horse. I did
ever stop talking
He said it with a D
How cool would it be to wake up tomorrow and just be like tomorrow all I gotta do is wake up eat breakfast
And just start pouring beers down my gullet and just join that'd be a great
You'd love that man
Oh, but I love it. I almost want to quit my job. Actually, I'm gonna call my boss tomorrow and be like beta said to quit this job
There was a guy at a baseball game, I don't know if you remember this this was like two years ago
Then there was a baseball there was a baseball player named digger
And he kept yelling it, hey digger, hey digger.
And they kicked them out, they banned them for life.
Remember that from the game?
They banned them for life, yeah.
They did, I remember that.
I don't want to repeat what you said,
but I do remember that.
That was awful, that's awful what they did.
But I think they came back, didn't they come back?
They led them back though, I think.
I think they thought about it and recognized what he said and realized he's actually a good guy and they let him back. That's what I'm thinking.
That's messed up though man. I mean wouldn't you think that there's a player named that and he's just yelling the player's name over and over again?
There's actually a football player whose first name is Noah and I'm not going to say his last name because I don't want to be banned from town.
But you can think about it. It starts with a K.
And then so the T
That's a band work who's your favorite football team got if I can ask the rate would he get in a football ball to more
It is
He used to be the Patriots and then Brady left and then it was the Buccaneers
Oh, so you, when your team ain't good, you just changed to another team.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
That's a big fan.
It was all about Brady.
It was all about fucking Brady.
And when Brady was in the past.
If I ever seen your real life, for you just admitting that to me, I'd fuck the fuck out
of you, boy.
When Brady was with the past, it was always...
the past and then they fucking shit on him and he left he went to the box you
want to fucking all right then after he retired then who you root for now now
the next one now now now it's the Ravens it is the Ravens yeah and then the
Ravens with Lamar six so you just move from winner to winner to winner that
ain't a fan hey what do you want you think I'm gonna back I want you to be a
real fucking fan I'm not gonna back a fucking loser I live in Chicago now you
Fuck you
Joe
Respect to be your god
Ravens have a good line, great receivers, the Marlfordy.
Thank you, Jamie's Cowboys.
That's a football fan right there in the chat.
That's a fan right there.
That's a football fan.
Go Ravens.
Ravens ain't one in a while.
They were in the FC Championship a year, two years ago.
Daddy's bigness.
The fuck kind of name is that?
Hey, your boy's back, psyche, he's back.
He jumped right up.
Yeah, we got Hopkins to as a number three
Look at him.
What's his name daddy?
Daddy bigness. Oh, I'm sorry about that. I thought it was
He was on he was on earlier. We got form bombed DB for all you straight guys up there
One thing I'll say to the people say we picked up Hopkins member this day flowers and Bateman are our number two and two
Receiver one and two. So the Andre Hopkins is the number three
He's gonna be playing against the other team shittiest cornerbacks. The Andre half is gonna he's gonna eat
So let me guess you listen to sports radio four hours a day every day
Well, we're not at work. Yeah, we're not doing my job
In the truck for hours
What up big
What up Joe you talk to me really mad. All right. Nice to meet you buddy. I can't
You first you first week out like a couple days ago
Oh, you want to say that again? You first me a couple days ago
Down a couple days ago. No, you cursed me out
He says you all
I get drunk sometimes. I never will cut you out. It's nice to meet you buddy. Who's your favorite football team if I can ask
I'm not I'm not into sports
Oh, you're in the ballerina. That's pretty nice.
I'm into strippers.
Strip girls.
Ooh, you're in love with a stripper.
Remember that.
No, it's nice to meet you man. I'm fucking with you. It's nice to meet you too, right?
Even though you're not into sports, I still like I guess you're my friends like it's kind of weird
I never had a friend that
I'm just a devil son
You're the devil son
What's what what's up with all that shit with the devil son? I'm Satan. I'm the evil one who's all these accounts. Oh, I don't know
Don't know about that. You know I'm talking about it. Yeah, I saw the videos, but I don't know. I don't know who's that
He's not doing a fucking evil gay laugh and all this shit. You're sure
I don't know
Have you been working outside? You look like you've been working out man. You've been looking really in good shape, buddy
I do thank you so much. I don't think I do
out
If I was gay
What go I guess why why why always this who we banned that word from the chat psych like gay what did you burn?
Yeah, can we it's not it's not an offensive term. It's over said though. Yeah, I'll just say the H word then
Yeah, there you go
Yeah, I don't like that
Clinical term
scientific so it's kind of like
Okay, calling you a homo-safety. We're not fucking scientists. All right
It's a little like there is a little like offensive because it's like so clinical. Let's just not be offensive up here
That's all let's try not to be offensive
Exactly we are joking around so
You know, I hate to say this like I haven't said in a while
Can you pull a card for me, please?
Sure one more time, please. Hold on. I'll pull this alien deck
Say one more time. Got it. I can hear you. I can hear you. I asked to the pull a card. How many shuffles do you want?
I think we all forget that this is a tarot channel, you know
It's like to you right to a panicles. So this is like
Keeping things balanced like see like your perfect symmetry like keeping it's like even if like the world is
Go and rough and crazy like yours. You're staying balance. It's like you see
Perfectly still so perfect
And the dark
Perfect balance. There you go. Where'd you get that back at soggy on you?
That's a big old set. That's a big deck of I've ever seen one. That's it. Yeah. Oh, thanks. Yeah
I have a new deck. I have a new deck to this is a new deck. I've already an Oracle card for this new deck
This is a cool deck. This is called this deck is called. It's called believe in your own magic. Okay. Oh, that's a good one
These are oracle cards
Three at least three shuffles. Okay, too, but you think you're magic
But you leave your magic. This has voyage here. I'll put on a full screen. All right a voyage
This voyage and it says that's you already have all the answers
That is true. Wow, cool. Thanks. I love you. That's you
I hope you enjoyed that.
Lol's by the way, come on. Lol is fine enough. You don't got to put an S at the end
Joe was fucking shit about saying good times chat good times kick them now look where he's at
You know what clumsy you suck art. I mean if that wasn't clumsy, I would take it seriously
But it's clumsy the old hang dog
Good times who goes to good times is talking about anything the guys lose
He's an old bum. He just sits there all fucking cross.
that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the only one that's the
Hello, it's like a rude version of Isaiah mule. It looks like you know what clumsy looks like a fucking Mexican
Puerto Rican clown from a fucking circus. Look at that cat sitting all proud. He's Mexican
I thought he was Chinese. That's a good cat right there. Shut the fuck up God when I'm talking if you're God you would do
I'm gonna you're always fucking talking man. That's the problem
Yeah, nigga turn fishing the fucking line finish your fucking thought
My thoughts over I was done ten minutes ago
Oh, thank goodness that motherfucker left. What happened to Lenore?
Norse here
She said she's outside
I probably you don't let Lenore in the house, huh?
The North outside she likes to be outside in the summertime
Let her outside man. Come on. It's a cat or two. He's a pit
Just getting fucked everywhere
to live in a
I had this squirrel, really?
Yeah, yeah.
That's a gift.
That's crazy.
You won't know that.
Yeah.
I'm gonna play it and then look over and I know that's cool
That's not funny, I haven't heard it before. It was disgusting. It was disgusting.
Fuck you, you had to pick it up, buddy.
It was big. It was a big spill, too.
When I lived in Latham, Raven did kill Rat, like broke his neck, but just spiced.
Because there was no blood.
There was no blood.
Aw, we have a special guest.
Raven bought me a rat.
Joe, shut up. We have a special guest. All the 1K is here.
Oh, he's special.
Aw, that's a special guest. That's my fucking cousin. That's my best friend, asshole.
Yup, he's there.
What's up?
That's a real man.
Finally we got a real man on the pack.
One time my dog
one time my dog
brought me back a midget
and I had to bury him.
Nice.
my dog brought me back a couple of people
all the people
what are you guys wired listen dude dude psych yeah what's up i was just on chris kays stream
and and he was saying that you look like you're overdosing on fentanyl so I'm just
trying to make sure that you're okay. Hey say it with a Spanish accent. Is it Chris Kay that like harasses
homeless people in their tents?
All he cares about you already came up here to check on you soggy. That's actually a real friend right there
I know you're Mexican though. They said that you were like
Fuck you man. You were uh, they said you were overdosing psych
No, yeah, I'm Mexican I'm African I speak fluent Spanish
Blue and span as he was in England was over eating. That's what they said. God. He was over eating again
That's why he's like under buckling down. Who's this taco show?
Your fucking mother's a taco show mommy
But my boy out he's here. I go a little crazy
Joe little
Antonio Gates
One of the best tight ends in the history of football is going to
hook up with nobody kids Saturday, nobody kids Saturday.
I just said, I said Saturday is all nobody kids, nobody kids.
Wait, what are you guys doing?
You don't care about football.
Why don't you guys say one thing?
I know I talk a lot already.
This guy, Gotti was like, I've never even played sports in my life.
I don't even like sports.
I never even played it.
Gotti, you're a woman.
You like ballerina.
You like basketball.
What are you talking about?
I play basketball at high school.
did you uh did you play Yu-Gi-Oh did you play Yu-Gi-Oh in middle school I did no no I
I played the last yes he did yes he did I did love that shit I love Pokemon I'm
all you guys I play Pokemon Pokemon was for the gay kids nobody plays that
oh my god Yu-Gi-Oh Yu-Gi-Oh was the shit if you're really you play Yu-Gi-Oh Yu-Gi-Oh that's what the
Yeah, okay, some people used to say that shit all the time one time. I was fucking walking home from school
What happened and I'm now and I'm shuffling through my deck
Big-ass deck of you your card and some kid walks up behind me one of my buddies and he fucking
Whips all my cards fifty two pick up and it goes all over everywhere
Did you cry I would do it I was about to cry when I was little but like
Looking back at it that shit was
where's my where's my blue eyes white dragon is that a new guy I don't know
yeah I've already talked about beada beada skitties is uh I think beada
skitties is the next gymnics she's gonna fucking end up fucking I mean listen
A lot of these girls, they're just like good times, but they're females.
Yeah, and Jim will cry like oh he abused me again abused me again
Take your fat ass back to the Chinese restaurant sit out front you fucking Buddha looking
Listen, are you talking to me or Jim Nick? Hold on. Are you talking to me or Jim Nick?
Major, come here. Let's go outside. I'll tell you right now
Major real quick on the stream. Let major get a panel
Yeah, they're right. I want to see major get the fuck out of here
the
black
I
I'm sure I'm sure clumsy as pissed you off before but his mom never did nothing to you bro. Don't bring
Don't bring his mama bro. His mom brought him into the world. No
You know, you know what it is. It's like when people start bringing people's families up. It's because they have no jokes to say
Yeah, you're not gonna attack me you're gonna attack my fucking like my parents. Yeah. Yeah
What's wrong with that? Yeah, you have nothing to say about me. So you're gonna attack my fucking family and my ancestors
You know fucking stupid that's
So you're telling me that clumsy made you so mad that you want to attack his family for
creating him like a guy made you so mad that you want to attack his family that have nothing
to do with it like think about it sounds stupid doesn't it?
Who are your fucking ancestors?
That's some pussy ass shit. Yeah, yeah, you know what and you're naming yourself God, bro
That's blasphemy bro. That's literally disrespecting
Disrespecting religion bro. That's disrespecting religion right?
well a huge population a huge percentage a huge percentage of the population of the world's
religion i'm gonna be disrespecting it if i'm god because you're naming yourself god you're not
Bro, if you were God, you'd think you'd be in a gay guy's podcast?
I'm right here, I'm right here, touch the light.
You'd be hanging out with a gay guy?
You're all fucking tested.
Yeah, that's right.
You're on the fucking list.
You're not God.
You're all on the fucking list.
Enjoy it.
You're the God of fucking faggots.
That's what the fuck you are.
the
Good times
Don't so you're so you're basically so you're
You're openly disrespecting God cuz you're gay
Disrespecting God
You'll see wait for it just wait for it
wait till this Thursday when the Lions play the charges and a football season kicks off
when that ball gets kicked off the start of the game when that kicker runs up and kicks the ball
Then the ball season 20-25 in here boys
I can't wait
Oh, I can't wait, you know what I can't wait for Joe
I can't wait we're on when they're on the field and the national anthem is going on
and the jets, the fire jets fly over the stadium.
Oh, they're going to be five, six, and two bombers by a band.
I am a hurricane.
Hold up, hold up.
Jay has a question.
Jay, go ahead.
What's your question, pal?
Thank you, man.
Don't be shy, Jay.
Don't be shy
Jay you're muted dumb black guy
Jay my answer is up nothing because they
Go back to what you were doing. That was a good story Jay
The real god
See the fake god didn't even know James ready to talk. See that's not a god. Yes. No, it's like you're sorry. I was testing Jay
Uh, where you want to test these fucking nuts.
Jay, you failed.
Oh!
What's your favorite football team is like I don't even watch sports. I never even played sports
so much. I've never ran in my life. I don't even know how to throw a football or a baseball.
Joe Shipley Joe Shipley have you ever like seen a dude that doesn't know how to throw a football like I fucking
When we were kids this guy Brad Brazil brought his uncle Scott to the field and it's uncle Scott. Let me turn my light on
His uncle Scott like through a baseball like this like it's already like and we were we all
almost kids made fun of him and his uncle ran home he was like 30 years old and we were like nine
his uncle ran crying bro bro i used to date this girl like her parents hated me and one time
i was throwing a football with her dad and this dude he threw a football like a straight pussy like
Bro, I could throw a football like I could throw a football like
Shit right now. I haven't thrown a football in a while
But the longest I've thrown a football is like 60 65 yards and like bro
I would go far back and like this forward throw the football at me
He wouldn't reach me and when I would throw the football at this guy
I get I get super close
So I get super close to him and because that nigga didn't like me I would throw bullets
I would throw fucking like
I would fire this football off at this dude's chest and it would be like it would fucking
bounce off this dude's hands and it would dude it was pissing him off like he didn't want to play
no more but it was just so funny bro god damn I know for sure that motherfucker still thinks about
Bro that fool no that fool hated me like cuz I was like
Yeah, I don't know
Mexican and shit. I don't know. They were like weird. They were a weird family
But yeah, bro that mother I got his ass good though bro imagine bro
Bro, imagine you have a daughter and and you hate her boyfriend and then you you go play catch with them
And it's just going darts. He's throwing darts at your fucking head and you can't catch them because they're going so fast
Well, I've been a psych I think psych is OD and look at him he fucking took his pills and he's out for the count
Yo, God! Yo, God! Do you know if he's dying? You're God, right?
the
I'll be there in five minutes
You just act like a god when she gets here be like, oh, I know everything I started the whole world
You fuck Joe Joe Kim just said shut the fuck up. All right
Robot's never said it's like you guys are pretty boring
Yo, can you put up put sigan put sigan you got you got motion like that?
There's room for one more up here.
Now there's room for one more to stick in.
He's not gonna make it.
Major, get up!
Major, come outside!
Come on!
Hey, John!
He's empty!
That dog's empty!
Oh, shit, dude.
What the fuck's up?
You got go.
Stop!
So I see did you get that blanket at the little big horn because it looks like sitting bulls?
See that ain't me. It's not even a fucking in the joke. Fuck you God
Don't blame me for everything Joe I
Was going to say so you shouldn't get your kids at the battle of little big one because it looks like that shit was made out of
Buffalo air
You just get out of prison dude, you look like you're gaining like 50 pounds, what the fuck?
I'm playing on buffalo skin, look at me, I'm a little buffalo man, buffalo man.
Stop, chill, chill.
You know the sound, little buffalo man.
I'm gonna tell you guys right now. All right, let's do a let's do a pull which all right
All right, so usually every year there's like three live streamers that died this year broke Malone died
This year broke Malone died. Um, who else has died this year?
Yeah, he died he got stabbed
by who?
I don't know
basically in his uh
broke balloon died
yeah in his obituary
it said that he died
in like a senseless attack so
he got like in a fight
somewhere and he got stabbed
basically from whatever
broke balloon died
I don't know
I don't know but he died
Kogan died the day after
Listen, listen, listen, listen
Broke Malone, you guys don't know about broke Malone because you guys don't know about lore you guys just started
You guys just started joining you guys just started joining streams and you guys just gossip like women like the view
You guys like
You guys talk like women and that's what you guys were known for.
This drama.
What was he known for?
Broke Malone was one of the first OG live streamers that streamed with us beside him.
He was one of the original people that streamed.
I have hair under my fucking head, and it's quite a fucking, look how gay it is.
It's dark, and you're probably wearing fucking that, too.
There's hair under it.
Shit.
That's nice.
Thank you, man.
It's like a fucking ginger pita griffin.
It's huge.
My hairline should be about right about y'all.
I mean a lot of these people that do these drama panels, bro
They don't know any lore. They don't know anything. They just try to like they're just trying to make easy money off of people
That I'm bought a two sag it's a razor rain. You won't come on
And let me see what else called me bald because you won't come on panel either so I can see your ugly ass
It's one thing to sit in the fucking chat and then make fun of people to have their camera on when you
I mean Joe, I'm gonna agree with Joe on that
I'm gonna agree with Joe on that at the end of the day. You can't you can't make fun. Listen
this and you can't make fun of someone's appearance if you're insecure about your own appearance
that's why you don't go on here
fuck we wanna make fun of you understand
you're insecure god you're insecure bro
you're insecure you can't take it bro
I'm insecure aren't you the 5-1 mexican looking dude
why are you crying about it
aren't you the 5-1 mexican dude that was flirting with psych the other day
No that's clumsy that's you you're the 5-1 Mexican dude with the
with the scuffed mustache you're that little five you're the little 5-1
major dude you're the 5-1 major dude that flirts with psych all the time
you're the one getting raped by yeah we know you are crying for mercy on that
Chicken Andy had me bent over. Yeah, remember that
When he fucking fucking raped your ass on the bus about three years ago
You were there you were fucking crying and you never touched me. I've hung out
You were crying and bleeding you dumb fuck you're thinking about
It was you you're talking about all jiezer and chicken and he fighting
You're talking about dope district
I know exactly what the fuck I'm talking about. I've got asshole chicken Andy never touched me
Listed this video of the whole fucking thing
There's a video of chicken Andy fighting Andy fucking raping you on the bus. Yes
Yes, yes, are you talking about Andy dick raping?
I don't know. I'm not fucking kicking Andy, raping only 1k on the bus.
You kicking Andy raped me on a bus?
Yes.
Where's the link?
Dude, dude, would you block it out?
What's the link?
It's this, I'm not fucking looking for it.
I'm telling you, you're thinking about adult district attacking me when I was passed out.
So he did rape you. Okay, so it was dope district who raped you not
Them to be honest you fucking piece. Thank you
To be honest, okay, I was wrong. No, but what I'm trying to like just tell you don't listen like
If you're gonna say something like just fucking like like say the truth bro cuz now like now it's like
Where is your whole life like people aren't gonna believe what you're saying. You don't even know what the fuck you're talking about
But you just open your lips
You don't even know what you're talking about, bro
I got the name wrong it was the other guy who fucking did it to you and I was and I was telling you and you were saying no
It's chicken Andy
I was trying to correct you bro. Bro. You don't even know what the fuck you're talking about
Yeah, I got raked bro, I got raked all right
But at the end of the day at the end of the day you're five one you're five one and you're over here
And you're over here stimpin for psych. All right. All right
So you're gonna get fucked by an old-ass dude. That's on drugs
Who that's kind of
I just said the psyche not on drugs. That's gonna rape me. I don't think so
I mean all trying to tell you is not that kind of drugs, bro. Sikes on drugs
That's why it's not here. No, just cuz you're used to doing it have it done to you doesn't mean everybody's gonna do it, man
Man, you're gay as shit, Gotti. You're a bitch, Bertie.
Joe, you're the gayest one of all, man.
What are you fucking kidding me?
You just gotta shut down, my god,
and then you're going to resort to calling me gay as shit.
Go fucking suck the Ravens' dick, you fucking clown.
Fucking bozo.
Hey, bozo.
Ronald McDonald, he wants his fucking eyebrows back.
Yeah, exactly.
Get him in here.
Get him in here, will you?
Shit.
Fucking Kim's even laughing at you for God's sake. Oh
Golden child slapping
I'll donate $50 just like if you turn your camera on for 20 seconds I'll donate $50 right
now to psych if you turn your camera on for 20 seconds.
We'll talk as chief do it and I will.
You're taking money out of Slick's pocket now. Now you're taking money out of Slick's pocket. Do it and I will if I don't do it
Obviously, he's gonna give you the money back. I don't do it
We gotta talk your head first. We gotta do it. Do it
Hey, don't work that way buddy. No, we don't work that way. You make the rules. Okay, so I'll put my camera on you
You won't give the money
You won't give the money and then I turn my camera off or nothing. No, I don't think so
All right. Well, if you want to speak Spanish that's on you. Okay
Send the money
Have I not sent 25 of it and then you show and then I send the other 25 go ahead. That's fair do it
I said nothing and beg for already to come back because he's my fucking
We don't give a fuck because it really doesn't matter that works to that could work that could work
If you guys want fucking pinups
Why why are you kicking me out though? This is in your panel
Why are you
You're mad I'm great. You're that mad bro. You're that triggered God you're that mad you're kicking me out
And it's not even your panel. Why don't you just make it? Why don't you just start your own stream?
Why don't you start your own string you out again? You want me to start your own string to kick you out again?
Pick me out faggot be good
Me out good time
Just witness you want to go you want to fucking go
Say the fuck your word, Joe!
Shut the fuck up, God!
You're out of here! He's out!
He's out! Out! You're out, Joe!
You're the fuck out of here!
Bag it we this is shit talking community
You're done
Fucked your wife you fat motherfucker
What oh I said
You know got to do already like that man. You ain't got to do my boy already like that
He's all right, he's okay, he's a good guy. I'm sorry, bro. He's trying my bad. I was being a dick